<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Exercise on Georgios Karamanis</title>
    <link>/categories/exercise/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Exercise on Georgios Karamanis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Georgios Karamanis</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 17:58:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/exercise/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Exercise 6</title>
      <link>/blog/2018/3/exercise-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 17:58:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018/3/exercise-6/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ndash; Suzanne Opton, Inspired by the News, The Photographer&#39;s Playbook, p. 256
That’s two in a row, it doesn’t go that well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exercise 5</title>
      <link>/blog/2018/3/exercise-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 17:55:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018/3/exercise-5/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ndash; Alison Morley, Tell Me a Story, The Photographer’s Playbook, p. 232</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exercise 4</title>
      <link>/blog/2018/3/exercise-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 18:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018/3/exercise-4/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ndash; Lorenzo De Rita, Alphabet of Assignments, The Photographer&#39;s Playbook, p. 81
The list of assignments in that page was more of an exercise in absurdity that the author made than a list of actual assignments. Examples are, &amp;ldquo;Demonstrate the validity of this emotional mathematics equation: 11+22=8&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Do everything you can to do nothing&amp;rdquo;, etc.
Anyway, I started collecting some question marks (one is greek):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exercise 3</title>
      <link>/blog/2018/2/exercise-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 18:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018/2/exercise-3/</guid>
      <description>Don’t look at the picture (assuming you used a digital camera). Go back home. Write a short text (half a page) about why you took that picture. Put it into envelope A. Write another short text (half a page) about what you remember the picture to look like in your viewfinder. Put it into another envelope, B. Once done, store everything and wait four weeks, not looking at either the picture or what you wrote.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exercise 2</title>
      <link>/blog/2018/2/exercise-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 18:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018/2/exercise-2/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ndash; Susan Lipper, Alter Ego, The Photographer&#39;s Playbook, p. 200</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exercise 1</title>
      <link>/blog/2018/2/exercise-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 18:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018/2/exercise-1/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ndash; Michael Northrup, Skipreading, The Photographer&#39;s Playbook, p. 250
  Houses   Blurred   The leftovers   People   Things behind glass  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>