<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Exercise on Georgios Karamanis</title>
    <link>/categories/exercise/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Exercise on Georgios Karamanis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Georgios Karamanis</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 17:58:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/exercise/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Exercise 6</title>
      <link>/blog/2018/3/exercise-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 17:58:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018/3/exercise-6/</guid>
      <description>Make a conceptual portrait based on a news story… Choose an ongoing or specific news item and make a photograph that reveals new insight into the story.  &amp;ndash; Suzanne Opton, Inspired by the News, The Photographer&amp;rsquo;s Playbook, p. 256
 ![](/images/2018-03-16-20183exercise-6/IMG_4390.JPG)  That’s two in a row, it doesn’t go that well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exercise 5</title>
      <link>/blog/2018/3/exercise-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 17:55:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018/3/exercise-5/</guid>
      <description> Tell me a story in five to seven pictures. It can be about anything, but it must have a beginning, middle and end. It can be about one person or one place or one thing.  &amp;ndash; Alison Morley, Tell Me a Story, The Photographer’s Playbook, p. 232
 ![](/images/2018-03-09-20183exercise-5/D0DCAF87-5EBA-4CF4-8014-406513B8E7CA.JPG)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exercise 4</title>
      <link>/blog/2018/3/exercise-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 18:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018/3/exercise-4/</guid>
      <description>h. Start a collection of question marks.  &amp;ndash; Lorenzo De Rita, Alphabet of Assignments, The Photographer&amp;rsquo;s Playbook, p. 81
The list of assignments in that page was more of an exercise in absurdity that the author made than a list of actual assignments. Examples are, &amp;ldquo;Demonstrate the validity of this emotional mathematics equation: 11+22=8&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Do everything you can to do nothing&amp;rdquo;, etc.
Anyway, I started collecting some question marks (one is greek):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exercise 3</title>
      <link>/blog/2018/2/exercise-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 18:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018/2/exercise-3/</guid>
      <description>Get out of the house and take one picture, spending no more than ten minutes to do so. Don’t look at the picture (assuming you used a digital camera). Go back home. Write a short text (half a page) about why you took that picture. Put it into envelope A. Write another short text (half a page) about what you remember the picture to look like in your viewfinder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exercise 2</title>
      <link>/blog/2018/2/exercise-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 18:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018/2/exercise-2/</guid>
      <description> Take a series of photographs that are not by you  &amp;ndash; Susan Lipper, Alter Ego, The Photographer&amp;rsquo;s Playbook, p. 200
 ![](/images/2018-02-16-20182exercise-2/IMG_4390.JPG)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exercise 1</title>
      <link>/blog/2018/2/exercise-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 18:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018/2/exercise-1/</guid>
      <description> Take fifteen random images from your archive and organize them into five different sequences. Explain your response to each.  &amp;ndash; Michael Northrup, Skipreading, The Photographer&amp;rsquo;s Playbook, p. 250
 Houses    Blurred    The leftovers    People    Things behind glass   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>